https://www.stonebriar.org/terms-of-use/

UPDATE: Read our response to Covid-19 (updated 12/9/20).   Learn More
Terms of Use
Overview
Stonebriar Community Church (SCC) is a non-profit organization.
This Privacy Policy covers SCCs treatment of personally identifiable information (Personal Data) that SCC gathers when its users access (view) and use the Web Site and when they use content and/or services on the Web Site. SCC knows that people (users) care about how their personal information is used and shared. We take your privacy just as seriously. So, please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.
By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to this Site, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of SCC and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States.
Information Collected Through the Site
We collect Personal Data through the Site when you voluntarily chose to provide us with Personal Data, through one or more of the following options:
Personal Data:
Registration – Our Site’s registration system may require individuals(users) to give us various Personal Data, including contact information such as their name and e-mail address, and demographic information such as a ZIP code, sex, or age. Such contact information is used to contact the user when necessary.
Surveys and Questionnaires – Any online surveys and questionnaires may ask individuals for contact and demographic information. The individuals contact information is used to contact the user when necessary.
Newsletters/RSS Feeds – Individuals may also choose to subscribe (opt-in) or to unsubscribe (opt-out) to newsletters or RSS feed on this website. This is further explained in the choice/opt-in or opt-out sections below.
Other Information:
Demographics – We receive and store certain types of information whenever individuals interact with our Site. SCC automatically receives and records information on our server logs from individuals browser including IP addresses, SCC cookie information, and the page requested. Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. SCC only uses this data in aggregate form. This as a statistical measure and would identify a user personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often people access parts of the Site so that we can make the Site appealing to as many people as possible, and improve the content. This information will not be shared with advertisers and other third parties.
Many companies offer programs that help you to visit web sites anonymously. While SCC will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.
IP Addresses – An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. Through the Site, we collect IP addresses in order to conduct system administration, report aggregate information to sponsors and advertisers, and to conduct Site analysis. If someone requests pages from the Site, our servers enter the visitor’s IP address into a log. To maintain visitor anonymity, we do not associate IP addresses with records containing Personal Data. However, we will use IP addresses to identify any user who refuses to comply with our in-house rules or terms of service, and to identify users who threaten our service, Site, customers, advertisers or others.
Cookies – Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that a Web site transfers to an individual’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. Our Site uses cookies during your online session to deliver content specific to your interests. Cookies allow us to customize your other message repeatedly. Our cookies do not collect or contain Personal Data. They do enable us to relate your use of the Site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to our Site. SCC does not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Data that would reveal the identity of a user, his/her user or screen name or email address.
Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Sites most attractive features.
Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information
We use the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by e-mail, will we use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the certain services available through the Site, we will use your Personal Data to provide access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. We may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Site to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site, to better understand our users and to improve our services. SCC may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future communications. In addition, at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or to have your name deleted from all of our mailing lists please contact us as indicated below.
If we intend on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.
Our Disclosure of your Personal Data and Other Information
SCC is not in the business of selling your Personal Data. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you and will not disclose your Personal Data to a third party except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:
Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: SCC, like many Churches, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing online givings. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide it with the information that it needs to perform its specific function and require that it keeps your Personal Data confidential and only uses it consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Legal Requirements: SCC may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of SCC, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.
Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Data may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.
External Links
In order to provide users with greater value, our Site may provide links to various third party websites. However, even if a third-party affiliation exists between the Site and that destination site, we do not exercise authority over these linked sites, each of which maintains independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. We do not assume responsibility or liability for these independent methods or actions and are not responsible for the independent policies or procedures of destination sites. We also cannot take responsibility for the privacy initiatives or the content of such web sites. These links to third party web sites are provided only for your convenience, and as such, you access them at your own risk.
However, we wish to ensure the integrity of the Site and its destination links, so any comments pertaining to the Site or any Sites accessed through these links are greatly appreciated.
Linking Your Website To Our Pages
We encourage you to link to our pages. However, we ask that you abide by the following guidelines when doing so:
You may not infer or imply that the Stonebriar Community Church sponsors or in any way approves of your site or any other site.
You may not frame, display, or alter any material from our web sites, or our web pages directly, in any way that obscures our identification, banners or site navigation. Framing does not allow users to bookmark the framed page. Also, some sites use frames to present content belonging to another site as if it was their own. We feel this is confusing to users and jeopardizes the integrity of our content. The presentation of the material linked to must make it readily apparent that the content is the property of Stonebriar Community Church or its affiliates.
You may not present Stonebriar Community Church website content as that of the site owner, otherwise misrepresent the content of the Stonebriar Community Church web pages or misinform users about the origin or ownership of the content of Stonebriar Community website.
You may not duplicate content (including recorded broadcast, video, graphics and/or photos) from this or any related Stonebriar Community Church websites without express written permission of the Stonebriar Community Church.
Exclusions
This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by SCC other than Personal Data collected through the Site. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to SCC through this Site or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as user profiles, comments, shared posts, prayer requests, birth announcements, memorial announcements and message boards (collectively, Public Areas) any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, Unsolicited Information). Please think carefully before disclosing Personal Data or other Unsolicited Information in a Public Area. All such Unsolicited Information is not confidential and SCC shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution and may be used by others in ways we cannot prevent for unauthorized purposes.
Children
SCC respects the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online.
We are a general audience site. We do not direct any of our content specifically at, nor do we knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under thirteen, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Site. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provider Personal Data on this Site without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to SCC through this Site, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases. We have implemented procedures to ensure that if we obtain actual knowledge of a child’s personal information we will take steps to delete that information. In addition, if SCC knows that a user is under age 13, we will NOT: (i) deliberately collect online contact information from that user without prior parental consent, except where used to respond directly to the child’s request; (ii)deliberately collect personally identifiable offline contact information from that user without prior parental consent; (iii) deliberately give that user the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior parental consent; (iv)distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information of that user without prior parental consent; and (v) entice that user by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.
Security
We employ reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the Personal Data under our control. We employ strict security measures to safeguard online transactions, including usernames and passwords. Personal Data is stored in a secured database and always sent via an encrypted Internet channel. However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this Site may not be secure. Therefore, you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.
Choice / Opt-In
Our Site gives users the opportunity to subscribe to receive newsletters and other communications from us. This Site also gives users the opportunity to stop receiving these communications at any time. You will find an opt-out option at the bottom of all communications.
Other Terms and Conditions
Your access to and use of this Site is subject to the Terms of Use
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your interaction with this Site, please click here to contact us online.
Stonebriar Community Church 4801 Legendary Drive Frisco, Texas 75034
Changes to this Privacy Policy
SCC may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used/collected. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Data, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site.
Copyright Notice
Stonebriar Community Church logos may not be used in connection with any product or service that in any manner disparages or discredits the Stonebriar Community Church.
Registered Trademarks
All website design, text, graphics, layout, music, recordings and content contained in this website are copyright © of Stonebriar Community Church and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All rights reserved.
Many requested uses are permitted by this policy, but if your intended use of the contents of this site are NOT expressly permitted herein, you may not : reproduce, upload, post , transmit, download or distribute any content, “mirror” or include this information on your own server or in your own documents; or modify or reuse the text or graphics on any of these websites without the written permission of the Stonebriar Community Church.
You may print copies of the material for incidental church and personal use. No content may be sold or used for any commercial purpose. Any printed copy must include copyright information.
You may link to content on a Stonebriar Community Website, provided you follow our Linking Policy.
Any other use of materials on this web site-including reproduction for purposes other than those noted above, modification, distribution, transmission, display, or republication-without the prior written permission of Stonebriar Community Church is strictly prohibited.
For more information, please e-mail your inquiry to webmaster@stonebriar.org
Disclaimer
THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED BY THE STONEBRIAR COMMUNITY CHURCH ON AS “AS IS” BASIS. WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE WEBSITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, OR MATERIALS INCLUDED ON THIS WEBSITE. STONEBRIAR COMMUNITY CHURCH WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.
Questions or Concerns
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at this site, please send us a detailed message at the e-mail address under the Contact Us link below. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
